This is your time.
I Used to Be Famous is a comedy, drama, music film directed by Eddie Sternberg.
A former boy band star unexpectedly gets a second shot at success
when he forms a bond with a gifted young drummer.
Vince, played by Ed Skrein.
Amber, played by Eleanor Matsuura.
Austin, played by Eoin Macken.
Dia, played by Kurt Egyiawan.
Dennis, played by Neil Stuke.
Mel, played by Racheal Ofori.
I Used to Be Famous is a 2022 British musical comedy-drama
film made by Forty Foot Pictures for Netflix.
Directed by Eddie Sternberg in his feature length debut, and
starring Ed Skrein, Eleanor Matsuura and Leo Long.
The film debuted on Netflix on 16 September 2022.
The film explores themes of autism, drum, singer, drum kit, autistic.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.